dailygames247.com 2013-04-04

# Daily Games - Play Free Online Flash Games at DailyGames247.com - Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy for http://www.dailygames247.com 

The privacy of our visitors http://www.dailygames247.com is important to us. 

**Privacy Policy:** We want our users to always be aware of any information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.

**Information Collection and Use:** We respect each site visitor's right to personal privacy. To that end, we collect and use information throughout our website only as disclosed in this Privacy Policy. This statement applies solely to information collected on this website. For each visitor to our website, our web server automatically recognizes no information regarding the domain or e-mail address.

The information we collect is: * used to improve the content of our Web page. * used to notify visitors about updates to our Web site. * Never shared with other organizations for commercial purposes.

Registration is not required to enter our site. However, subscription to certain services may require a user to complete a registration form. During registration a user must give certain contact information, but we never sell or give away this information. It is only gathered to contact the user about services on our site for which s/he has expressed interest. It is optional for the user to provide demographic information (income level, gender, etc.), and unique identifiers (username, password, etc.). Giving additional information helps provide a more personalized experience on our site, but is not required. We publish a newsletter, and we never sell or share our subscribers' email or mailing addresses. We operate online surveys, and we never sell or share our subscribers' email addresses. We do show advertisement to our users, which is handled by [Google Adsense](http://www.google.com/) & [ValueClick.com](https://www.valueclickmedia.com/). So any such concerns with our advertising should be directed to them respected.

**Google and the DoubleClick DART cookie:**

* Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site. * Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit and other sites on the Internet. * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy. ](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html)

**To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit[networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/)**.

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>
